{
    "subject": "Clint_Buchanan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Lindsay_Rappaport",
    "human_readable": "Clint Buchanan is married to Lindsay Rappaport.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9322384595870972,
            "question": "To whom is Lindsay Rappaport married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9240642189979553,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Clint Buchanan and Lindsay Rappaport?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9178138971328735,
            "question": "Is Lindsay Rappaport married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9025745391845703,
            "question": "Name one person married to Clint Buchanan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9023550152778625,
            "question": "Who is Clint Buchanan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.821910560131073,
            "question": "Who is Clint Buchanan's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7386453747749329,
            "question": "Is Lindsay Rappaport in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7197735905647278,
            "question": "What is the name of Clint Buchanan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5852420330047607,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of Clint Buchanan's partner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4756726920604706,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with Clint Buchanan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clint Buchanan is married to Lindsay Rappaport.",
            "html": "yago_25796_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of Clint Buchanan's partner?",
            "html": "yago_25796_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Clint Buchanan's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_25796_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lindsay Rappaport in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_25796_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25796_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can determine that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Clint Buchanan and Lindsay Rappaport being married, and then getting a divorce due to various reasons. This suggests that they were indeed married at some point in time, supporting the triple statement."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents indicate multiple instances where Clint Buchanan and Lindsay Rappaport are mentioned as being married. For example, from document 91.txt: \"Over the course of a short time, they fell in love, married in 2000 and shared a love story of a lifetime.\" And from document 73.txt: \"The two of went to Las Vegas together to find Lindsay's son, Will Rappaport and bring him back to Llanview. While Clint and Lindsay were in Las Vegas they got married.\" These statements support the triple that Clint Buchanan is married to Lindsay Rappaport."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}